[[-1, 1, 1, "rene speck", "", "", "", 1, 2, 17074, 17075, 10, 2, 0, 5, 3, -54, "PER", 10, 0, 0, 0, 10.0, 0, "LOC", "PER"], [-1, 1, 1, "rene", "NOUN", "NN", "O", 0, 0, 17072, 17073, 10, 3, 1, 8, 5, -12, "PER", 10, 0, 0, 0, 10.0, 0, "LOC", "PER"], [-1, 1, 2, "speck", "NOUN", "NN", "O", 0, 0, 17076, 17077, 10, 7, 0, 0, 7, -4, "LOC", 10, 0, 0, 0, 10.0, 0, "LOC", "PER"], [-1, 1, 3, "was", "VERB", "VBD", "O", 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [-1, 1, 4, "born", "VERB", "VBN", "O", 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [-1, 1, 5, "in", "ADP", "IN", "O", 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [-1, 1, 6, "germany", "NOUN", "NN", "O", 0, 0, 95, 96, 10, 7, 0, 1, 6, 22, "LOC", 10, 3, 3, 4, 0.0, 1, "PER", "LOC"], [-1, 1, 7, "but", "CONJ", "CC", "O", 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [-1, 1, 8, "likes", "VERB", "VBZ", "O", 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [-1, 1, 9, "nyc", "NOUN", "NNS", "O", 0, 0, 2291, 2292, 10, 8, 0, 0, 8, 40, "LOC", 10, 1, 9, 0, 0.0, 8, "ORG", "LOC"]]